(Detecting Badges)
It's hot today
Take rest under the shades
Where are Suneo
Hurts
What?
It's Nobita, sorry
So, you're up in the tree
I's looking for you
Naigber community team
want to play game with us
Tomorrow 9:00 meet at the ground
ls that right?
Got to find the other 3
in this hot weather
So hot
That's why I don't want
to be a manager
He's not in
ls ShioCho in ?
Where is Jian?
I was going to ask you
He is helping at the store
Everyone is not in
They should tell where
they're going
It's Nobita
Manager, what are you doing?
What am I doing ?
Of course I'm...
Don't complaint
this is manager's job, isn't it
Dorn
You keep complaining
So, as long as you know where
they are
That's right
Ah, so tired
Give you this
What is this
It's shinny, so cute
A badge for us ?
May I ? It looks very expensive
It' ok, take it
Nobita, you're so kind
I like it
must worth of something
So pretty, thank you
They're all so shinny
Why should I give them gifts ?
Those are detectors
Detector ?
This is a radar map
Detector“ send out waves
And show on the map
As long as you remember
who badges give to
You'll know who is where
Those 4 are still on the field
Ah, they start moving
It seems they're fighting
The 3 run away
Jian is after Shanten
Ah, they are getting closer
Shanten is caught
Seems to be beaten up
Run away again
Run further and further
Finally
Ah, back to his house, safe!
How interesting
Ok, let me call him
Shanten, it hurts so bad
being beaten up, poor baby
How did you know, Nobita ?
I saw the others too
Kusan didn't move at all
since the very beginning
Must be hiding
Ah, Suneo, where is Suneo ?
Stops at the ice cream shop
Buying ice cream again
Good
You seem to be very busy
Customer, you've got a phone call
Me?
Hello, this Suneo
How is your ice cream taste like ?
Too much ice cream will melt
your teeth
It's Jian
Run in a very high speed
Ah, I know
Must be his mom found that out
And is chasing after him
everywhere
Enjoy yourself
Get into the field and hide
Should be under the tree shadow
Heart mark is Shizuka
How hateful, she's going toward
Jian
No!
They get together
how disgusting
How can they be together?
What are they doing ?
Are you kidding
I'll get Jian for this
And Shizuka is too dare
Makes me so angry
Dorn
Where is Jian?
He was just here?
Don't be nonsense
there's only me
But on the map...
You guys sticked together
How gross
That stupid Jian
Idiot, what has he done ?
Ah
say that again
So, he hid inside of the pipe
Where is Lianfu ?
He's so hopeless
Madam, if you needed help
I can help you
Lianfu is reading comics at
comic shop
Really?
I am sure where they are
I was told that you know
where the kids are ?
Tell me where is Jian ?
Don't try to hide him from me
He's hiding in the pipe on the
field
Where is my Yantsi?
Where is our Chenmei?
Thank you
The disgusting Jian
So, the map can help people
I was beaten up
My mom scolded me
Me too
Nobita seems to know
where we are
I think it's kind of scary
I hate Nobita for that
How can he know?
Wait, maybe
This badge ?
It must be
why don't we do this
They all jump into the pool
in the park
Everyone all jumped together
I remember it was near here
Nobita
No wonder you're so kind
to us
Dorn
Help
Don't run, my mom beatened me
and I beat you
Weird, it's so incredible
The 5 go to the toilet
of park and never come out
Let me check
Did you see Nobita?
Can't find him anywhere
Ah
Nobita
Doraemon
Don't let any one find out
snick me out
So stink
Please be patient and save me
Please, help me
(Forgetful bird)
I'm going now
Be careful on the way
Dad, wait
Don't forget the model you
promised last night
You promised
T-TURBO 984 car model
Don't forget
All right, I'll remember
I'm going honey
Be careful on the way
Wonder if it would be any
problem
Daddy is always so forgetful
No problem
Trust your daddy
and be patient
Mr. Yet, you forgot your thing
Umbrella
Thanks, I forgot it all
Really, if you lost it again
Your wife will scold on you
Thanks so much
You've remind me every time
It's ok, then bye now
Thank you again, truly sorry
I'm forgetful lately
Right
I promised Nobita
Welcome, may I help you
I want to buy some model
Yes, what kind?
Oh, no
What kind of model did he want?
Ah, what is it?
352 or
How terrible
Well, I'm so sorry
Wonder if daddy will come home
soon
You've being worried about this
Your daddy will be back soon
Nobita wanted model so bad
this time
I can understand how you feel
Uh, I can't wait
The model is so cool
Right, Doraemon
I'll make one for you too
I'm back
It's Daddy
I'm home
Daddy, welcome home
Didn't bring anything with you
Daddy, where is my model?
Sorry, I'm sorry
I forgot the name of the model
So, you didn't buy it ?
I'm sorry
I went to the toy shop
Didn't forget my promise
It's the same
Any way, you didn't buy it
That's why I keep reminding you
Sorry, I'll buy it tomorrow
Honey, how can you promise
like that
What if you forgot again
that would be terrible
Ah, honey, where is your
briefcase
Oh, no, I forgot
Umbrella and briefcase
I've called your friend
Go get it from him tomorrow
Umbrella, briefcase and model
You can't miss anyone of it
you've to bring them back
Yes, I'm so sorry
Ok, honey, I'm starven
It's dinner time
Ah? Honey, you didn't go today?
Where? Anything happened?
You forget again
You're invited to a friend's
house,today
Oh, ya!
Look at you, you forgot again
You're too forgetful, honey
Nonsense, people forget things
sometimes
All right, I'm leaving now
Ah, honey
What, now what?
Mail this letter for me
Ok, I know
Remember, the letter is very
important
I know it
Don't be like last time
put it in pocket for a month
You're so nagging
Trust me, will you ?
Daddy is going out now
Are you going to buy model
for me?
No, that will be tomorrow
Daddy is going to visit some
friends
How boring
Then, I'm going
Honey, the letter, the letter
Look at you , you forgot again
Oh, no, I forgot again
That's very terrible of you
Sorry
I'll be losing confidence soon
Daddy, since you're forgetful
Ask Doraemon to help you
Doraemon,
think of something
Well...
Got it, use this
The forgetful bird
Put it on your ear,
then it'd be all right
When you're about to forget
it will remind you
Oh, so convenient
How interesting
Let's try it
Daddy, would you get in the
house
Ok
Daddy, come try it now
Pretend that you forget to
bring the letter
Like this
You forgot You forgot
All right
So, this is a good thing
Thank you Doraemon
then I feel relax now
No matter, how forgetful I am
I can't forget to mail
the letter
So, do it on my way back
Oh, and the bird to remind you
Mr. Yet, are you kidding
No, it's real
Otherwise, I can show you
Uh, I wonder if there's
Got it, pretend that I forgot this
wallet
I leave the wallet here and
go straight home
The bye
You forgot You forgot
Just like this
How about it?
How interesting
Let us see
Do you want to try ?
You forgot You forgot
Oh, no, I'm still cooking
Great, good to have the bird
Yes, and that makes everyone
laugh
And then? Did you mail the letter?
The letter?
Oh, no
I've forgot the letter and
the wallet and the bird
Here you go again
Hopeless
(Vending machine)
I want to have a camera
When I go out to buy things
I save the changes
But it's still not enough
Nobita
Go get something
Yh? Going out buying things?
I'll go, I'll go
Buy a bag of cherry for me
Hey, I'm not dumb buying 150 Yen
cigarette with 150 Yen
That way you don't get any change
Give me 10000 yen bill
I'll be happy to go buy it
Daddy is angry
I know it's meaningless
But I still have to go
I'm sorry, daddy
Why do you sound so happy?
Must be some vending machine
Go get it again
Find Doraemon to go
with you
It's not in
Can't do anything
left the thing here
What is this?
Looks like a vending machine
Wonder what this is
If this can show cherry
then it would be so wonderful
Let's try
Should put the money here
Pull the stick?
I only put 150 Yen
And so many things come out
ls the machine broken ?
Good, here comes cigarette
Cherry brand
Cherry should be in red with
white back ground
It shows Cherry brand here
New package?
How did you buy so many with
150 Yen
If you ask me
I don't know either
Don't be so nagging
So
It's a cigarette machine
But, Doraemon leaves this
It shouldn't be a ordinary one
How can it be ?
Like, everything will come out
from it
The ink is out
Go buy some
Put in 250 Yen
Touch the botten randomly
This time I want ink
Uh, the ink I've never seen
Price 30 Chen ?
Why did you buy so many ?
I don't know
Miss it so much
Hey, this is a cigarette from
Choho time
I remember it was 10 Chen
Choho time?
I know it
The machine is some kind of
time machine
Buy things with cheaper price
from the past
What if I can buy a camera with
the money I have now
It should be cheaper
I'll set it to long time ago
Hesho
Nothing come out
Not enough money ?
What's wrong, what's wrong?
200 Yen is not enough ?
The machine is cheating
I'll beat you up, dorn
No camera out?
Those are the money I saved for
a long time
What is this ?
Do you thing they would have
camera in Nailian Time ?
Oh, yes, can't set it too early
How much money you have left ?
30 Yen
Then..should be able to buy it at
this time
Oh, rare camera
With this model you can't buy
the film for it
That is too much
Without film, camera is useless
I can't stand it
That's what you get when you use
this vending machine
You can use it to buy things
But can never use to make money
Make money ?
Ya, use this to make money
Make enough money to buy
new camera
Can buy any ancient stationary ?
With half price ?
However, cash please
Fountain Pen 1 Yen and 40 Chen
Candy 10 Chen
Chocolate 30 Chen
Pencil 4 Chen
Ok, buy 1 Yen pencil
So cheap
The design is so special
Now, I can make a lot of money
Everyone will be so happy
I make money too
Nothing can be better than this
Keep like this
I'll become a billionaire
Come celebrate
Use the machine to buy something
good to eat
Eat something that have
never had
Yes, this is a time machine
Can buy things from
the future
Desert from 100 years later
Good
First time to taste this
Taste of hearty
Oh, yes, not paid yet
How much?
23 thousand Yen
What? I can't pay it
Help
Doraemon
Doraemon, come help me
I don't have 23 thousand Yen
I can't help
That's too much
(Grandpa in the dream)
Son
Hey, son!
Dad is that you ?
Long time no see
You look fine, very good
I was worried about one thing
so I come to you
About Nobita
You seem to spoil him a bit
Since you say so
it seems like it
Boys should be trained strictly
Dad
More training
More strictly
It's not good if keep it
like this
Dad, did your soul say that?
Not soul, it's dream talk
But, it's quite right
You've spoiled him too much
For Nobita, I'll think about it
Daddy, buy comics for me
Don't read those meaningless
comics, go study
You've been yelled at? How rare !
Children shouldn't be afraid of
wind and rain
Go play baseball
It's so cold, I'll die
Throw the ball
What kind of posture is that ?
Throw the ball seriously
What happened to daddy
become so strict
It hurts
Idiot !
Go, fetch the ball back
What? Been beatened up ?
How can you be a man?
If someone beat you,
beat him back
If you didn't win,
don't come home
Wait, dad
Daddy was trained by your
grandpa like this
So that you can grow strong
So terrible
It's because grandpa
nagging in dream
What kind of person
your grandpa was?
Don't know
he died before I was born
I want to see him
Go see him then
This is the house before
reconstruction
We're back to 30 years ago
Where did he hide?
No use
Run away is no use
Go home
Come if you dare
Your hands and legs were all
frozen
Can't show your weakness
You must be trained
body and mind
Understand ?
No
Comics are no meanings
But everyone has it
He said friends can borrow
each others'
Kid without comics will be
pressured
It's grandmom
She's so gentle since very young
Don't do it
Still, didn't get to buy it
Hey, did you bring any comics
today?
What? You break your promise
again !
Because my father
If you're beatened up why didn't
beat him back?
Go again
If not win, don't come back
The devil grandpa
Honey
Something you'll love to eat
No, save them for the kids
Yes
You'd better go look at him
Take the medicine and bandage
with you
Ah...
The money is
For him to buy the comics
Honey, you can buy it back
The child will be so happy
It's impossible to take back
my words
You must pretend I don't know
This kid
Coming out now
Minding things Devil Oldman
Who are you ?
We are...
Here through the time machine
From 30 years' future
My dad is your son
Terrible
I don't know what you're
talking about
But look into your eyes
can tell you're not lying
Any way, I'm your grandson
It is like this
Yes, look just like my son
Looks very smart
First time to have someone say
that I'm smart
Come just in good time, eat slowly
People said grandson is always
so cute, it's true
What? Your daddy bully you ?
It's all your fault
I don't know about that
It's your daddy's dream
But we were all in trouble
You should be responsible
Hey, son
be gentle to Nobita
Great
(Paper Machineman)
Player on the east is Suneo
On the west is Nobita
Go for it the two of you
Get ready
Ready, start
Can't tell who's wining yet
The result comes out
Suneo won
Filling the score board
No. 1, Jian
No.2 Suneo and Shizuka
No. 4 Nobita
They even said
I can' even win playing paper sumo
I'm SO angry
Dorn, just wait and see
Doraemon
Not the tissue paper
I want those kind of thick,
hard, can't be pressed paper
Paper sumo
can be made out of card board
I want to win
so I need something even better
There's kind of good paper
Really
Uh
This is it
Paper machineman
Use this to cut out a machineman
Just like really, it can move
Really?
This is it
We butterfly
You make one
Right away
Finished
Can't how good it is
You see, it's moving
Tell him, not to practice here
The house's going to be destroyed
Cool
This should be winning
Everyone will be surprised
Continue to play
Everyone has gone home
How come?
It took me a longtime
to make sumo
I don't want to play now
My mom wants me
to mow the grass
Got it
Doraemon, lend me the paper
Ok
I'll do the mowing
See, the lamp eat up all the grass
Thank you
I invite everyone over
Shizuka
Come play paper sumo
No one is home now
I have to stay, can't go out
Let the dog watch the house
I'll go look for Jian,
you go first
Jian, come play
He took the bus to
buy something
Forget it
No, I want to chase the bus
You're doing this time
Wait and see
Good, finished
Get in hurry
Start the car, and run
Where is the bus?
There
Go
Stop, the bus in the front
Wait
Wait, wait, wait
Nobita
How many times do you want
to loss?
Come and start
You never give up
I don't want to be in trouble
Decide to deal with you 3 by
myself
What? So proud?
Ready
Start
Can't tell if winning or not
How can it be, unforgivable
once more
No matter how many times
Can't tell if winning or not
The paper men were too proud
I want to tear it apart
Stop STOP
Nobita's Sumo won
(Black belt Nobita)
Nobita
Don't bumping around at home
Go outside to play
Yes
My father is teaching me Judo
How brave
Want me to teach you ?
Teach me, teach me
I want to learn too
Really, since you all say so
Now, don't have to Wait for
next time
No, not now
First of all, do like this
Too cool
How about it. So good to use
Like a Judo black belt
Then, I was beatened up like this
What? You're bully
and come home quietly
Fight back if you're a man
Throw the Jian out
But I'm afraid
Hopeless
Each time is like this,
how sad
Doraemon
lend me something to make me strong
Tickles, It tickles
Stop
You only want to rely on me with
one thing
Each time the same
Black belt
What is this ?
Let people become top Judo player
special black belt
It that right?
Just tight this up, then you'll
become strong
No matter how strong the opposite is
Touch you once, then be thrown
out by you
Then
I can go to Jian and revenge
Yes
Doraemon Thank you
Don't touch me, don't touch me
Once touched will be thrown out
automatically
You Jian
you should have know my power
Can't let just anyone touch you
I know, I'll be careful Bye
My target is only one - Jian
Here he comes
Wait and see
Come play Judo again
Come if you dare
Are you out of your mind ?
You're too weak, too dumb
I have no time with you
Wait, wait, wait
Suneo, Jian wait
Please
Be quiet
Leave him alone
Good, then I'll come to you
Coming
So annoying
What is he doing ?
Don't go
It hurts
Dorn
It hurts, go away
Nobita
What is the matter with you?
Shizuka
You're all muddy
Don't touch me
I just want to help to get
the mud off
No, don't touch me
don't touch me
You're so dirty like this
Oh, no, help
It really throws her out
I'm sorry, forgive me
Why are you doing this ?
I'm sorry I apology to you
Let me down
Hey, how can you bully girls
This kid is hopeless
Teacher please don't touch me
it's dangerous
Are you threatening me?
No use. Hold it there
Didn't I just say so
Unforgivable
Stop I want to teach you
Don't touch me,
don't touch me
Scare me
What's that sound
Little brother
can you borrow us some money ?
I don't have any money
No money?
go home and get it
Don't have money
at home either
Want to be beatened up
Want to get hurt?
Bad kids from middle high
Those rascals
I'll show them my konfu
I'm here to wrap you down
Who are you
Run when you can
I'm not going to get hurt
What a idiot
Shut up and come
You buster
Dorn little kid,
don't be so proud
So strong
Just like in the comic book
Am I dreaming
Doraemon, give you back
the black belt
Where is Doraemon
Where do I usually put the belt?
Ah, here
This is not my belt
Never mind, it's good looking
Oh, ya ?
Don't put it on, daddy
It's throwing again
Honey, what happened to you?
Honey
The way mom tie the belt
is weird
Can't untie it
Before the belt is untied
Better don't go near daddy
You guys think of something
to untie the belt
Daddy, open your mouth
Open your mouth again
Open your mouth
Daddy, don't be angry
Wait
we'll think of something then
(Super Mixer)
Don't run Shilon
Don't fight
You're too much
Stop, stop, stop
Shizuka, what's wrong
They always fight when
they're together
Can't understand them
why can't they be nice
Don't fight
What
just because of this
Because it has two
Just mix the two,
then it'll be ok
I have good thing
Super mixer
Connect the both ends to dog
and cat
Like this
Just like this
Yes
Then turn on the power
Doraemon, where are they?
Relax, you just wait and see
Great Shizuka
Bye
Buying something strange again
This is very expensive
Wasting of money
You mean, where should we put
this ?
We don't have any space for it
Give it back
Poor daddy
Help him out
Ok, use super mixer
Mom, don't be so angry
I'll take care of this
Doraemon, are you ready?
Connect this end to the pot
Connect this end to bathtub
Ok, that's it
Just mix the pot and tub
Daddy, the water is ready
Go take a bath hurry
Daddy does not want to take a
bath
Never mind
This is...
Cool
Just like the king of
The Night of Arabic
What had happened ?
Honey honey
wake up
Cool
Didn't expect to be so happy
Honey
What happened to me?
He stayed in the bath too long
Let mix some more
Doraemon
Uh, mix more to make the house
bigger
Where did you put the vacuum
cleaner
Nobita, did you see vacuum cleaner
I mixed it with the trash can
So, don't have to throw trash
one by one
Does it help ?
Feeling kind of strange
Ok, mix some more
Right, to let Mom and Dad to be
even closer
Thank you both
Become so convenient
I buy some give for you
Thank you Dad, Mom
So many red bean cakes
Thank you
It's weird, where is the TV
Where is it?
Daddy, TV is here
Where ?
Heso
Look
TV is mixed up with coffee table
It looks so inconvenient
Sorry, excuse me
Can't see anything
I'm busy
Iron is kind of weird
And become so heavy
We a toaster
Hot
What is this, lighter and shaver
How is it, convenient isn't it?
Lighter and shaver
can use together?
Nobita, did you see the radio
Come Daddy
It's S hit, a hit
Radio is mixed with telephone
Where is refrig ?
Mom, here
Honey, wake up
We mix the refrig with toilet
Nobita, Doraemon
you're too much
This is too much
Put them back all at once
We did this for Mom and Dad
Here goes my red bean cake
So does the model
I thought it's a good idea
This is to punish your mischief
Only one desert for two of you
What only one red bean cake
I don't just have half
Me either
Got it
Let's use the super mixer
Nobita did you set it
OK
Turn on the power
We made it
Big success
Mixed Nobita and Doraemon
Becomes Dora-bita
Body and mind together
And if always be one
You don't have to divide
the cake
Good
Go out to play
No, I want to take a nap
I want to play
No, I want to sleep
Play
Sleep
Something sounds weird
Play
Sleep
(The making of desert island)
Ah?
What's the matter
My petty money is cut short
Mine too
I want to protest
Right
How much to reduce this month
for cigarette
The rend it up this month
Not enough money to use
I can't help then
Only if you can build our home
Then, no need to pay rend
Saying is easy
Now
want to buy a land in Japan
So expensive ?
Is there land making machine
You're talking nonsense again
Where are you going to put the
land you manufactured
Find a field to put it
Ya? No Way
Want to somewhere else
Ya
Right
Put it on the sea
Yes, construct a small island
But...
can island be constructed
Let the volcano explode from
bottom of sea
Try to find lava on the shoal
Lava
Rocks melted into liquid
Right, lava is light
and will float on the surface
So, let lava
break out from the shell
Forms the volcano island
Let's find lava through
volcano
Can't understand very well
anyway, just look
This is the volcano area of Japan
Near Tokyo
Let's dive into this area
and search
But I can't not swim
Not to worry about that
You can breath with airpipe
in the water
Deep sea petrolium can take
the water pressure
Smoke cigarette like this is sad
I'll think of something for
daddy to smoke happily
Not have to pay rend any more
I want to finish
Tiger Tank today
I want to make Wuchan war ship
Compare what I'm doing now
your's all too childish
Let's go
Doraemon
how big a island can you make?
It depends on the amount of lava
Perhaps it'll be some
around here
Go
Use lava detector
If we walk on top of lava
it'll make a sound
About the island we're making
Can we share the land with
everyone
Sure
Wait How about Jian and Suneo
I'm going now
Wait, wait, wait
I'm not crazy about them
But I can't leave them out
Ok, share some with them then
3.3Meter
To Shizuka, 1000square meters
Then she'll look at me
differently
We've been walking so far,
still not find any
Be quiet
it has never been easy
Name the island Nobita Island
No, that's not fair to
Doraemon
Call it Doraemon Island
Which do you like best?
I'm tired
Nobita , you're too impatient
Sea is very huge
Here
How can you make it explode
High power rock melting machine
What do you do with this tool ?
This is very important
First, to soften the shell
Then wait for the lava to break
through shell and explode
Strong shaking
Let's leave hurry
After few days,
the island is formed
We'll use subway to connect
roads to island
Right, build a subway to get
there in 10 minutes
I'm waiting for Doraemon
Island to be finished
Next time when you build a house
I want a room with 20 tatami
And make father a study room
and mother a napping room
I's wrong
please forgive me
Let me joint
Can we joint too
What is a Doraemon Island
You just have to wait
I can't wait
This 7 o'clock morning news
Firstly
a new island was found
This morning 80 Km from
Bachan on the sea
A new island was found
On the screen now
is shooting from the helicopter
It's already finished
Let's go see
It's our island
Nobita Island
Ya, ya, we make it
Let's build a house on the hill
A baseball field on the platform
And a park and play ground
Such a big area
Do whatever you want
Someone's there
Really
Let's go see
I'm here first
I'm first
My company want to build a
play ground here
What
my company want to build villa here
Please leave everyone
Small island formed on Japan sea
Belongs to the nation
Please don't tease us
Take us to Doraemon Island
Take us there hurry
Nobita
what's wrong?
your land is not formed yet?
Doraemon, build the land
in the air please
(The end )